<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Om</string>

    <!--Quotes -->
    <string name="login_quote">Meditate so that mind cannot complicate life!</string>
    <string name="landing_quote">Meditation brings wisdom :)</string>
    <string name="welString">Take a Deep Breath </string>
    <string name="meditation">Meditation</string>
    <string name="calm">Calm</string>
    <string name="helptosleep">Help to Sleep</string>
    <string name="music">Music</string>
    <string name="zen_meditation">Zen Meditation (Zazen): - Means “seated Zen” or “seated meditation” HOW TO DO IT It is generally practiced seated on the floor over a mat and cushion, with crossed</string>
    <string name="vipassana_meditation">means “insight” or “clear seeing”
        HOW TO DO IT
        one is to sit on a cushion on the floor, cross-legged, with your spine erect; alternatively, a
        chair may be used, but the back should not be supported.</string>
    
    <string name="mindfullness_meditation">Mindfulness of breathing, practice of intentionally focusing on
        the present moment
        HOW TO DO IT
        Pay close attention to the movement of your breath. When you breath in, be aware that you
        are breathing in, and how it feels. When you breath out, be aware you are breathing out.</string>
    
    <string name="loving_kindness_meditation">(Metta Meditation): - boosting one’s ability to empathize
        with others; development of positive emotions through compassion, including a more loving
        attitude towards oneself
        HOW TO DO IT
        Sit down in a meditation position, with closed eyes. Develop feeling of kindness and
        benevolence. Process it by thinking of first oneself then a good friend then a neutral friend
        then a difficult person and then gradually the entire universe</string>
    <string name="mantra_meditation">A mantra (OM) is repeated for the purpose of
        focusing your mind.
        HOW TO DO IT
        it is usually practiced sitting with spine erect, and eyes closed. The practitioner then repeats the
        mantra in his mind, silently, over and over again during the whole session. the mantra is actually
        whispered very lightly and softly, as an aid to concentration.</string>
    <string name="transcendtal_meditation">Transcendental Meditation is a specific form of
        Mantra Meditation introduced by Maharishi Mahesh Yogi. It is a widely practiced form of
        meditation, many sponsored by the organization, demonstrating the benefits of the
        practice.
        HOW TO DO IT
        TM involves the use of a mantra and is practiced for 15–20 minutes twice per day while
        sitting with one’s eyes closed.</string>
    <string name="yoga_meditation">its highest goal spiritual purification and Self-Knowledge.
        Various Yoga Meditations are: -
         Third Eye Meditation — focusing the attention on the “spot between the
        eyebrows”.
         Chakra Meditation — the practitioner focuses on one of the seven chakras of the
        body (“centers of energy”).
         Gazing Meditation (Trataka) — fixing the gaze on an external object, typically a
        candle, image or a symbol
         Kundalini Meditation — this is a very complex system of practice. The goal is the
        awakening of the “kundalini energy”.
         Kriya Yoga — is a set of energizations, breathing, and meditation exercises taught
        by Paramahamsa Yogananda.
         Sound Meditation (Nada Yoga) — focusing on sound. Starts with meditation on
        “external sounds”, such as calming ambient music, whereby the student focuses all
        his attention on just hearing, as a help to quieten and collect the mind.
         Pranayama — breathing regulation. It is not exactly meditation, but an excellent
        practice to calm the mind and prepare it for meditation.</string>
    <string name="self_enquiry_meditation">It means to “investigate” our true nature, to find
        the answer to the “Who am I?”
        HOW TO DO
        practice is very simple, but also very subtle. It is there, in some form or another, behind all
        your thoughts, emotions, memories, and perceptions. There is no special position to
        practice, although the general suggestions about posture and environment are helpful for
        beginners.</string>
    <string name="guided_meditation">It is an easier way to start, and you will find guided meditations
        based on several of the above traditions.
        HOW TO DO IT
        Guided meditation usually comes in the form of audio (file, podcast, CD), and sometimes audio and
        video.</string>
</resources>

